l'd smack you with a glove, but just last
week, I packed away my winter things.
It's the 21 st century,
you can't have a duel.
(Leonard:)Hang on, Howard.
(Leonard:)Barry, how good of a shot are you?
Not pistols. Minds.
A trivia contest.
And you may choose the field of battle.
Star Trek trivia,
Star Trek: Next Generation trivia...
...Star Trek: Deep Space Nine trivia,
Star Trek: Voyagertrivia...
...or model trains.
You have an advantage in trivia.
You have an eidetic memory.
Plus, I haven't watched Star Trek...
...since I discovered the strip club
near my apartment has a free buffet.
It's hard to find something
you're both equally good at.
ls there anything
you're equally bad at?
- Sports.
(Leonard:)All right, this is one-on-one,
first to five wins the office.
(Leonard:)Any questions? Yes, Sheldon.